{
    "id": "1d54851334524fc6a0ff8cc580849f8c",
    "title": "Prepositions Of Time",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "e6bbf5d8cffc4a7e99eba81bcc8ed512",
            "title": "Prepositions Of Time",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I will call you …………………….. Friday.",
                    "description": "We use on with days.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They got married ………………………… the week after Christmas.",
                    "description": "We use in with longer periods like weeks.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They are having a party ………………………… Easter Monday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "My birthday is ……………………….. May 18th.",
                    "description": "We use on before dates.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Chennai is hot …………………………. summer.",
                    "description": "We use in with seasons. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are you doing …………………………… the weekend?",
                    "description": "On the weekend is more common in American English and at the weekend is common in British English.",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am visiting my parents ………………………….. Christmas day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The palace was built …………………………….. the 16th century.",
                    "description": "We use in with longer periods like centuries. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I work best …………………………… the evening.",
                    "description": "We use in with evening, morning and afternoon.",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "See you …………………………… Sunday morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We met ……………………………. a cold evening in January.",
                    "description": "We use on before evening when we say which evening we are talking about.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They finished the job …………………………… a week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}